http://www.ndtsolutions.net/privacy-notice/

NDTS :: Privacy Notice
SITE MAP | PRIVACY NOTICE
HomeCompanyProductsMAUS V SystemsMAUS VDR11VACRSDual VacMAUS RotoArray4" Stroke Linear Air SlideEddy Current ProductsEddy Current ProbesEddy Current StandardsEddy Current InstrumentsETher NDESSEC IIIUltrasonic Testing ProductsUltrasonic TransducersUltrasonic StandardsUltrasonic InstrumentsFlawInspectaPragmaUltrasonic CouplantsUV LampsLumazonRobotic InspectionGenesis NSpect 210WebstoreServicesSupportServices & RepairInspectionTrainingConsultingCustom Engineering SolutionsNewsContactContact UsRequest Quote
NDTS PRIVACY NOTICEThank you for your interest in the Privacy Policy of NDT Solutions, Inc. (further referred to as “NDTS”). This Privacy Policy is to inform site visitors about how/why NDTS uses and collects user information.Do we use Cookies or Tracers? Currently, NDTS does not contain/employ cookies and/or tracers. However, the use of cookies/tracers is subject to change. If the change does occur, the Privacy Policy will reflect that change.Collection of personal information: In some cases, NDTS requests personally identifiable information from you in order to satisfy a transaction or for form submissions (quotes, service, etc). Examples of personally identifiable information include names, email addresses, mailing addresses, and the like.Disclosure of information: We do not rent, sell, or trade any personally identifiable information about you (e.g., e-mail addresses) to third parties. Certain NDTS Sites may disclose information to third parties assisting us in processing a transaction requested by you (e.g., credit card service providers). However, in order to cooperate with legitimate governmental requests, subpoenas, or court orders, or to protect NDTS and/or NDTS's systems and customers, or to ensure the integrity and operation of NDTS and/or NDTS's business and systems, NDTS may access and disclose any information it considers necessary or appropriate under the circumstances.External links: For the convenience of our site visitors, NDTS  may provide links to third party web sites. These websites are not operated or controlled by NDTS, and NDTS is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such external websites.Policy updates: From time to time, NDTS may revise this Privacy Policy at its discretion. We note the date of the policy below, so you know when it was last updated. NDTS advises you to check back periodically to review the Privacy Policy because users of the Site will be prospectively bound by the then-current version of this Privacy Policy.Revised: Aug 24, 2012
NDT Solutions10-1 Airport Road, New Richmond, WI 54017Phone: (715) 246-0433   Fax: (715) 246-0466www.ndts.comCage Code 1Q535
Terms & Conditions
©Copyright 2018, NDT Solutions - All Rights Reserved
